in this tutorial we'll be going over
在本教程中，我们将复习
some of the ways in which you can warp
一些你可以扭曲的方式
and distort objects in inkscape by using
和扭曲Inkscape中的对象
various path effects so to get started
各种路径效果，以便开始使用
we'll have a look at the envelope
我们要看一下信封
deformation path effect I have this text
变形路径效果我有这样的文字
object on my screen here I'm going to
对象在我的屏幕上我要在这里
convert this from text to a path by
通过以下方式将其从文本转换为路径
selecting it and going to path and
选择它并转到路径和
selecting object to path and now I'll
选择路径中的对象，现在我将
open up my path effects menu by going to
通过转到打开我的路径效果菜单
path and selecting path
路径和选择路径
effects from the menu I'm going to click
我要点击的菜单中的效果
this plus icon down here to add a new
单击此处的加号图标可添加新的
path effect
路径效应
and the path effect I'm looking for is
我正在寻找的路径效应是
envelope deformation so I'm going to
封套变形，所以我要
select
选择
that and let me zoom in on this so I can
然后让我放大这个，这样我就可以
see it better and if you notice in the
看得更清楚，如果您注意到
menu over here we have four different
菜单在这里，我们有四种不同的
ways in which we can distort this object
我们可以以何种方式扭曲这个物体
top bottom left and right so if I click
上、下、左、右，所以如果我点击
this button right here bend the top path
这里的按钮使顶部路径弯曲
we're going to get this green line on
我们要把这条绿线开通
the canvas you could take that green
你可以拿到那块绿色的帆布
line and move that up like that so you
排成一条线，像这样向上移动，这样你就可以
end up with that effect right there and
到头来就会有这样的效果
you can click on each node and change
您可以单击每个节点并更改
these handles so that you get this warp
这些手柄让你得到这个曲线度
effect as you can see here and I'll do
效果就像你在这里看到的，我会这样做
the same thing down here with the bottom
下面的底部也是一样的情况
path I'll change that as
路径，我会将其更改为
well and if you want to change the right
好的，如果你想改变右翼
and left path you could just click the
和左侧路径，您只需点击
buttons for those as well you can bring
你也可以带上那些纽扣
this in or you could bring it out like
或者你可以像这样把它拿出来
that and I'll do the same thing over
然后我会重新做同样的事情
here for the left path like this I'll
在这里，像这样走左边的小路，我会
bring this one
把这件拿来
in and then we end up with that effect
然后我们就会得到这样的效果
right there and then we have these other
就在那里，然后我们有这些其他的
options over here that we can enable as
我们可以在此处启用的选项
well so if I toggle off the left and
所以如果我把左边的
right paths we end up with this effect
正确的道路，我们最终会有这样的效果
right right there and since this is a
就在那里，因为这是一个
path effect this is temporary and can be
路径效应这是暂时的，可能是
undone at any time by just toggling off
只需关闭即可随时撤消
the visibility of the path effect right
路径效果的可见性右图
there or you can remove it by pressing
您也可以通过按将其删除
the minus button right there so I'll
减号按钮就在那里，所以我会
turn that back on if you want to
如果你想的话就把它打开
finalize the effect just go to path
最终确定效果只需转到Path
object to path and now you can grab your
对象到路径，现在您可以获取您的
nodes tool and you can see that this is
Nodes工具，您可以看到这是
finalized and the path has been warped
最终敲定，道路已经弯曲
so another way in which you can warp
所以另一种你可以扭曲的方式
objects and inkscape is by using the
对象和Inkscape是通过使用
bend path effect which allows you to
弯曲路径效果，允许您
bend an object along a linear path so a
沿线性路径弯曲对象，以便
good example for this here I have this
这是一个很好的例子，我有这个
drawing of a lion and let's say I wanted
画一只狮子，比方说我想
to add a tail to this Lon I created this
为了给这个Lon添加一个尾巴，我创建了这个
simple little tail using an intersecting
使用相交的简单小尾巴
area between two circles and a triangle
两个圆和一个三角形之间的面积
and I unified it all together so I'm
我把它统一在一起，所以我
going to place the tail on the lion here
我要把尾巴放在狮子身上
and to make this look curved so it looks
为了让它看起来是弯曲的，所以它看起来
more natural I'm going to go to the path
更自然的是，我要走上这条路
effects menu and I'm going to add a new
效果菜单，我要添加一个新的
path
路径
effect and the path effect I'm looking
我正在寻找的效果和路径效果
for this time is Bend so I'm actually
因为这次是Bend所以我实际上是
going to type it up here so I could find
我要在这里打字，这样我就能找到
it Bend there we go
它转弯了，我们就走了
and now if you click this button over
现在如果你点击这个按钮
here where it says Bend path you have
此处显示的是您拥有的弯曲路径
this green line that you can edit so I
这条绿线可以编辑，这样我就可以
could take this and pull this down like
可以拿着这个，像这样把它拉下来
that and as you can see there the path
如你所见，这条小路
is being or the object rather is being
是存在还是客体是存在
bent along that Green Path and you could
沿着那条绿色的小路弯腰，你可以
adjust these handles and you could take
调整这些手柄，你就可以拿到
this handle over here if you need to
如果你需要的话，这个把手在这里
make this wider like
把这个弄大一点，就像
that just like that and there we go we
就像这样，我们就这样走了
have now we have a bent path that looks
现在我们有一条弯曲的小路，看起来
more natural like a lion's tail and the
更自然，就像狮子的尾巴和
final path effect we'll be having a look
最终的路径效果，我们将会看到
at is the lattice deformation which
AT是晶格形变，它
gives you multiple points in which you
为您提供多个点，您可以
can warp an object so if I select my
可以扭曲对象，所以如果我选择我的
subject here and I add a path effect I'm
主题在这里，我添加了一个路径效应
going to look for lattice
去寻找晶格
deformation there we go and once you
变形了，我们走了，一旦你
have that applied you can come over here
有了这一点，你可以来这里
to your edit pads by nodes tool and you
添加到您的按节点编辑板工具，并且您
can see we have this blue grid with
可以看到我们有这个蓝色的网格
nodes placed on it and you could take
把节点放在上面，你可以拿到
these nodes and move them around like
这些节点并像这样移动它们
this to distort the object so if I go
这会扭曲物体，所以如果我去
like that I can make the subject taller
这样我就可以把对象做得更高了
or shorter and can warp and distort it
或更短，可能会扭曲和扭曲它
in various ways so that it doesn't look
以不同的方式，这样它看起来不会
so so much like the original object
太像原来的物体了
there like that and if I select my
就像这样，如果我选择我的
selection tool and toggle this off you
选择工具，并将其关闭
could see the difference there we were
可以看出我们之间的不同
able to warp this object rather easily
能够相当容易地扭曲这个物体
using that path effect so that's just a
使用路径效应，所以这只是一个
few of the ways in which you can warp
你可以扭曲的方式很少
and distort objects in inkscape if you
并扭曲Inkscape中的对象，如果您
found this lesson useful then consider
觉得这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private Community where you
甚至拥有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
你只需支付月费就可以了
$17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次17美元，你就会被判终身监禁
have some information about that down
我有一些关于这方面的信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想要将其查看为
always thanks for watching
永远感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]